{"data":[{"question":"________ a lot of other people, we managed to survive the recession.","a":"Contrary to","b":"In contrast to","c":"On the contrary with","d":"In contrast with","answer":"2","explain":"\n- In contrast to sbd\/sth: a difference between people, ideas, situations, things etc that are being compared.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"22","type":"1"},{"question":"If you ________ me, just say so.","a":"disagree with","b":"differ from","c":"differ with","d":"differ by","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Disagree with sbd: to have or express a different opinion from someone else.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"22","type":"1"},{"question":"If you don't like this one, try something ________.","a":"other","b":"more","c":"else","d":"another","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Else: [used after words beginning with \"some-\",\u00a0\"every-\",\u00a0\"any-\", and\u00a0\"no-\", and after question words]: besides or in addition to someone or something.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"22","type":"1"},{"question":"How much should I charge ________ giving her all that advice?","a":"by","b":"because of","c":"owing to","d":"for","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Charge for: be responsible for.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"22","type":"1"},{"question":"A lot of houses in our neighborhood ________ repairing.","a":"demand","b":"need","c":"require","d":"use","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Something needs doing: used when saying that something should have something done to it, or has to have something done to it.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"22","type":"1"},{"question":"I didn't realize you were a foreigner. Your ________ of English is very good.","a":"knowledge","b":"quality","c":"skill","d":"speech","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Skill of: an ability to do something well, especially because you have learned and practised it, eg:\u00a0technical\/management\/practical etc skill.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"22","type":"1"},{"question":"Oh, dear, I see we've ________ coffee. Do you mind drinking tea?","a":"done without","b":"gone off","c":"run out of","d":"turned out","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Run out of: to use all of something and not have any more left.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"22","type":"1"},{"question":"I have a very bad ________ for names.","a":"imagination","b":"memory","c":"mind","d":"thought","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Memory: someone's ability to remember things, places, experiences.\u00a0\n- Have a bad\/poor\/terrible etc memory.\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"22","type":"1"},{"question":"When someone is old he is in his second ________.","a":"child","b":"childhood","c":"childish","d":"childlike","answer":"2","explain":"\n- First\/second...+ Noun.\u00a0\n- Childhood: the period of time when you are a child.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"22","type":"1"},{"question":"She is ________ to leave as soon as possible.","a":"cautious","b":"anxious","c":"worried","d":"nervous","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Anxious to do sth: feeling strongly that you want to do something or want something to happen.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"22","type":"1"}]}